Hunter Posey

Mountain View, California 94041 | 205-495-7446 | ihunterposey@gmail.com Github | Blogs | LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript based programming with knowledge of various frameworks within JavaScript, such as React. Through my research and studies in Environmental Science and GIS technologies, I attained skills in problem solving, leadership, and teamwork that drive the production of amazing software.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, React, HTML/CSS, Git, Linux, Adobe Creative Suite(Photoshop, Illustrator, XD), jQuery, JSON, postGres, WireFraming, arcGIS, ESRI.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Vinylfy - Github | Demo

Vinylfi connects users/sellers to the niche market of buying/selling vinyl records in a fun and easy to use manner.

- Utilized sessions storage to create and persist user data.
- Implemented Auth for all new user information.
- Constructed analytical functions from the backend.

Sopranos Quote-Taker - Github | Demo

A simple and fun app where users can keep track of their favorite Sopranos quotes.

- Full CRUD
- SPA(Single Page Application)

AirDok - Github(Frontend) | Github(Backend) | Demo

A functional app that connects users to private airplane hangar owners to rent/reserve their services.

- Implemented the use of token storage for creating and saving new users.
- Backend Models Authenticated for signup/login, with error messages firing.
- Used serializers for the backend to allow ease of use for the complex relationships.
- Data is user generated with room for stretch goals to be easily implemented.
- Built out functionality for the checkout feature.

EXPERIENCE

Genesis Capital Ventures

Executive Assistant

Aspen, Colorado 01/2015 - 05/2015

- Created contracts for approximately 30 high-value clients per week.
- Managed client-relationships through 5-6 meetings per week.

Mountain High Outfitters

Back-of-house Manager

Tuscaloosa, Alabama 06/2016 - 02/2019

- Oversaw back-of-house operations(shipments, ordering, moving product, inventory).
- Managed \$25,000 worth of inventory.
- Assisted an average of 20 customers per day in regards to their needs.

EDUCATION

Flatiron School

San Francisco, California

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

11/2020 - 03/2021

University of Alabama

Tuscaloosa, Alabama

BA in Environmental Geography/GIS

05/ 2019